<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8"?><!DOCTYPE dita PUBLIC "-//OASIS//DTD DITA Composite//EN" "ditabase.dtd"><dita><topic id="topic_81ab0fa4-b481-489e-95d6-3bfa5a7b15c4"><title id="Title">Getting ready</title><prolog id="id-b633c5cf-98b7-4588-dfe2-6ff68efc060b"><author id="id-73613419-4047-4bf0-cf86-739e9a5db847">constant.gordon@gmail.com</author><critdates id="id-45ae30eb-3373-4e9e-d17b-cdb895f234b4"><created date="2017-04-24" id="id-028ba82a-e2e6-4e96-b88e-495505f7c4b9" /><revised modified="2017-04-24" id="id-af03a5a3-5765-4c63-86dc-9c69cfb105e1" /></critdates><permissions view="" id="id-f4149e49-0371-4473-8eb2-e9f608c055c4" /><metadata id="id-6eeba16a-11e3-443a-b7cc-f5efb253c466"><category id="id-b5e91779-9667-47f3-eb38-d93cfefe1a5e">Information Object</category></metadata></prolog><body id="id-7106f44d-2301-4de3-8b95-f725254a207a"><p id="id-6dc63880-09c6-495d-d7dc-904edd4103b0">Constant started with a broad interest in technology
                as a Master of Physics at the Technical University Eindhoven. His first job was as a
                marketing reseacher for integrated circuits (ICs), applying the logical thinking in
                making macro economic models for the IC markets, the IC inventory in the market and
                the IC production capacity worldwide.</p><p id="id-1fd62d7e-aa38-40ba-bfce-9db0aa7c2b1c">Industrial engineering became his second job where much was learned about logisitics, cost price calculation and development project planning.</p><p id="id-c84964f2-c428-4bbd-b2e9-b206b17b50ea">The understanding of market movement combined with detailed knowledge of production processes lead to his next job as sales support manager, becoming responsible for technology guidance to customers as well as the specification for products to be built. It is in this job that Constant started learning about managing product designers and the path for people to change their ways of working from technology driven development to customer requirement driven development and optimizing the technologies already in use.</p><p id="id-1d2cc32e-1eea-42a0-9c69-0086c8afc635">From being responsible for specifications with the help of technical authors and illustrators, Constant later became responsible for setting up a new way of working for NXP semiconductors.</p></body></topic></dita>
